<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Sshit Thc</title>
	<atom:link href="httpsshit.thc.org/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>httpsshit.thc.org</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 17:34:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Dembele signs five-year deal with PSG</title>
		<link>httpsshit.thc.org/dembele-signs-five-year-deal-with-psg/</link>
					<comments>httpsshit.thc.org/dembele-signs-five-year-deal-with-psg/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 17:34:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">httpsshit.thc.org/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[France international Ousmane Dembele has signed a five-year deal with Paris Saint-Germain from Barcelona, the Ligue 1 champions announced on Saturday. The 26-year-old Dembele, who was part of France’s 2018 World Cup-winning squad, joined Barcelona in 2017 from Borussia Dortmund and had extended his contract last year until 2024. PSG took advantage of the player’s ... <a title="Dembele signs five-year deal with PSG" class="read-more" href="httpsshit.thc.org/dembele-signs-five-year-deal-with-psg/" aria-label="More on Dembele signs five-year deal with PSG">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>France international Ousmane Dembele has signed a five-year deal with Paris Saint-Germain from Barcelona, the Ligue 1 champions announced on Saturday.</p>
<p>The 26-year-old Dembele, who was part of France’s 2018 World Cup-winning squad, joined Barcelona in 2017 from Borussia Dortmund and had extended his contract last year until 2024.</p>
<p>PSG took advantage of the player’s €50 million ($54 million) release clause to sign the former Rennes forward.</p>
<p>“I’m very happy to join Paris Saint-Germain and can’t wait to play in my new colours,” Dembele said in a PSG statement.</p>
<p>“I hope to continue to grow here and make all who love the club proud.”</p>
<p>Dembele, who has 37 caps for France and scored four goals, joins three other World Cup winners at PSG – Kylian Mbappé, Presnel Kimpembe and Lucas Hernandez.</p>
<p>He is the club’s ninth summer signing after defenders Milan Skriniar and Lucas Hernandez, midfielders Manuel Ugarte and Cher Ndour, forwards Marco Asensio, Lee Kang-in and Goncalo Ramos and goalkeeper Arnau Tenas.</p>
<p>At Barcelona, despite early problems adjusting to the Catalan side and injuries, Dembele scored 40 goals in 185 matches, winning three league titles in 2018, 2019 and 2023 and two Spanish Cups 2018 and 2021.</p>
<p>PSG are bolstering their attacking options with the futures of stars Kylian Mbappe and Neymar still uncertain.</p>
<p>“The passion and determination shown by Ousmane when he joined PSG is fantastic and is the attitude required for all our players,” said PSG president Nasser Al-Khelaifi.</p>
<p>“We are proud to have another French World Cup winner in Paris Saint-Germain at the moment. to enter a new great era for our club.”</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>httpsshit.thc.org/dembele-signs-five-year-deal-with-psg/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Security alert prompts Eiffel Tower evacuation</title>
		<link>httpsshit.thc.org/security-alert-prompts-eiffel-tower-evacuation/</link>
					<comments>httpsshit.thc.org/security-alert-prompts-eiffel-tower-evacuation/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[paglaadmins]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 17:33:17 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">httpsshit.thc.org/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A security alert Saturday prompted the evacuation of three floors of the Eiffel Tower in central Paris, France&#8217;s most emblematic symbol which drew 6.2 million visitors last year. SETE, the body which runs the site, said bomb disposal experts as well as police were scouring the area, including a restaurant located on one of the ... <a title="Security alert prompts Eiffel Tower evacuation" class="read-more" href="httpsshit.thc.org/security-alert-prompts-eiffel-tower-evacuation/" aria-label="More on Security alert prompts Eiffel Tower evacuation">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A security alert Saturday prompted the evacuation of three floors of the Eiffel Tower in central Paris, France&#8217;s most emblematic symbol which drew 6.2 million visitors last year.</p>
<p>SETE, the body which runs the site, said bomb disposal experts as well as police were scouring the area, including a restaurant located on one of the floors.</p>
<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s a usual procedure in this kind of situation which however is rare,&#8221; a spokeswoman said.</p>
<p>Visitors were evacuated from both the three floors and the square under the monument shortly after 1:30 pm (1130 GMT).</p>
<p>Construction work on the tower began in January 1887 and was finished on March 31, 1889. It received two million visitors during the World&#8217;s Fair of 1889.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>httpsshit.thc.org/security-alert-prompts-eiffel-tower-evacuation/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
